why did you wake up
你为什么醒来
Still drinking secretly
还在偷偷喝酒
Can't sleep
睡不着
Do you have any concerns?
您有什么顾虑吗？
not any
没有任何
let's go
我们走吧
Don't go today
今天别去
Let's take a day off
我们休息一天吧
Persons eligible for payroll deductions
符合工资扣除资格的人员
I send it to you
我发给你
Breakfast is ready
早餐准备好了
We'll send it to you
我们发给你吧
no thanks
不，谢谢
I've already called a cab.
我已经叫车了。
drink lots of milk
喝大量牛奶
Good morning
早上好
Delayed contact
延迟联系
Convenient transportation
交通便利
goodbye
再见
target appearance
目标外观
Girl rides a taxi alone.
女孩独自乘坐出租车。
group catch up
小组赶上
The second group stayed and continued to wait for Xiangyi.
第二组留下来，继续等待翔伊。
reception
接待
what do you do now?
你现在做什么？
I think mission accomplished.
我认为任务已经完成。
No need to rush back
没必要急着回来
available through her
可以通过她获得
High-speed rail details
高铁详情
Not yet
还不说
Can it be processed cleanly?
能加工干净吗？
Okay, I'll get rid of it.
好的，我会把它处理掉。
No
不
Can maintain relationship
可以维持关系
A girl who looks like Xiu Gen
一个长得像修根的女孩
after awhile
过了一会儿
I started thinking about getting married
我开始考虑结婚的事
you must take precautions
你必须采取预防措施
Why do girls always want to get married?
为什么女孩子总是想结婚？
not all girls
不是所有女孩
like me
跟我一样
Why is the report false?
为何报告是假的？
I have no idea
我不知道
I really don't know anything
我真的什么都不知道
Yao Yao
姚瑶
I want to go on a business trip.
我想去出差。
Yes
是的
Not an executive
不是行政人员
Didn't I tell you last time?
上次不是跟你说过了吗？
It's really in my hands
真的在我手中
There's still a lot of work to be done
还有很多工作要做
I really can't walk
我真的走不动了
put it on top
放在上面
explain
说
You should follow me too.
你也应该关注我。
I heard
我听说
Mr. Zhou directly asked me to do this.
周总直接叫我这么做。
A bit hard
有点辛苦
All flights are booked
所有航班均已预订
when
什么时候
this afternoon
今天下午
Get ready quickly
赶快准备
No, I think it's too rushed.
不，我觉得这太仓促了。
No more days
没有日子了
Just easy clean up
只需轻松清理即可
OK
行
Hey
嘿
why so suddenly
为什么这么突然
boss order
老板命令
There's nothing I can do
我也无能为力
but
但
Our mission is not yet complete.
我们的使命还没有完成。
I know
我知道
This is a normal business trip for the company
此次是公司正常出差
Nothing to do with games
与游戏无关
That would be good
那样就好了
Let's keep in touch
让我们保持联系
be safe
注意安全
Bangkok.
曼谷。
The task has not passed inspection.
该任务尚未通过检查。
How long does a typical review take?
一般审核需要多长时间？
As soon as 1 or 2 hours
最快1或2小时
If late it will take 1 or 2 days
如果迟到则需要1或2天
I'm not worried
我并不担心
But Yaoyao
但瑶瑶
This is a sudden business trip.
这是一次突然的出差。
where did you go
你去哪儿
Bangkok.
曼谷。
I'm usually on a business trip.
我通常在出差。
I don't
我没有
I'm a little too sensitive
我有点太敏感了
more sensitive than insensitive
比不敏感更敏感
She was on a business trip a few days ago
前几天她出差了
You have to stay in touch with her.
你必须和她保持联系。
I know
我知道
How's your investigation going?
你的调查进行得怎么样了？
The biggest question was last week.
最大的问题是上周。
Third floor leadership network
三楼领导网络
Have you encountered any problems?
你遇到过问题吗？
I checked the repair log.
我检查了修复日志。
No possibility of unraveling
没有解开的可能
you think
您认为
This network failure
这次网络故障
this is artificial
这是人工的
More than you think
比你想像中的还要多
How to disconnect from the network
如何断开网络连接
You might even think about nails.
您甚至可能会想到指甲。
I don’t know if there is a little bit
不知道有没有一点点
their network department
他们的网络部门
if there is a person
如果有一个人
So what do you want me to do?
那你想让我做什么？
Spies are usually in a department
间谍通常在一个部门
Set goals for two people
为两个人设定目标
One person supports another person
一个人支持另一个人
knew
知道了
Then I
然后我
along this line
沿着这条线
try to investigate
尝试调查
feel their bottoms
感受他们的底部
Be careful
当心
The nail could be right next to you
钉子可能就在你旁边
knew
知道了
stay alert
保持警惕
no one believes
没有人相信
Good evening
晚上好
welcome
欢迎
Do you have an ID card?
你有身份证吗？
yes
是
Thanks.
谢谢。
I think
我认为
Mr. Zhou is always interested in you.
周先生总是对你感兴趣。
What does it mean?
这是什么意思？
in his eyes
在他眼里
we are a flock of sheep
我们是一群羊
Play pig eat tiger
扮猪吃老虎
Get him off
让他下车
You said he was yours, right?
你说他是你的，对吗？
he is not interested in me
他对我不感兴趣
rather than falling into someone's hands
而不是落入某人手中
I better give it to you
我最好把它给你
I'm not interested in him either
我对他也不感兴趣
Why
为什么
young and talented
年轻而有才华
Handsome and rich
又帅又有钱
So I'll leave it to you
所以我就把它留给你
Yaoyao arrives in Bangkok.
瑶瑶抵达曼谷。
I haven't seen her for a long time.
我已经很久没见到她了。
It hurts a little
有点痛
she forgot
她忘了
I will arrange it
我会安排的
Zhu Yan
朱言
Tsugai Japanese Language Institute
津海外日本语学院
PhD in English
英文科博士
after graduation
毕业之后
Direct access to the High Speed ​​Rail Group
直接进入高铁集团
Responsible for translation
负责翻译
Qin area
秦地区
According to the High Speed ​​Rail Group
据高铁集团介绍
Provide a list
提供清单
Zhu Yan
朱言
Be a member of the bidding team
是投标小组成员之一
The main responsibilities are
主要职责是
Tag translation work
标签翻译工作
Can touch
可以触摸
The most important secret of bidding
投标最重要的秘密
is our standard
是我们的标准
first
第一的
we must expose
我们必须揭露
This red letter
这个红字
Is she a spy?
她是间谍吗？
Portraits attract users
肖像吸引用户
from me
从我
when you see something you know
当你看到你所知道的东西时
Zhu Yan has never been abroad.
朱颜从未出过国。
I have no background in studying abroad.
我没有出国留学的背景。
her social life
她的社交生活
it's easy
这很容易
In addition to the company
除了公司之外
The only place she goes the most
她唯一去得最多的地方
There is a yoga studio near my home
我家附近有一个瑜伽馆
I read it again
我又看了一遍
Xiu Gong’s SNS
修贡的SNS
look
看
She hasn't appeared for a long time
她已经很久没有出现了
love sign
爱的标志
After meeting Xiao Yi
遇见小毅后
The only one that belongs to her
唯一属于她的
love journey
爱情之旅
They were together recently
他们最近才在一起
SNS from Xiugen
来自修根的SNS
seen it already
看过了
She started last month
她从上个月就开始了
be able to share their photos
能够分享他们的照片
but
但
SNS of this program
本节目的SNS
Strange
奇怪的
his account
他的帐户
Newly registered 3 months ago
3个月前新注册
In addition to sharing
除了分享之外
Information about the racing circuit
有关赛车场的信息
in other words
换句话说
His love life with Shu Yan
他和舒颜的爱情日常
there is nothing
没有什么
personal information about him
有关他个人的信息
So this account is
所以这个账户是
look more
看起来更多
For Shu Yan
为了舒妍
I specifically applied
我专门申请了
what do you think?
你怎么认为？
like
喜欢
This is an elaborate scam.
这是一个精心策划的骗局。
what do you think?
你怎么认为？
certainly
当然
Enter the world of spies
走进间谍的世界
no love
没有爱
love aside
爱放在一边
This high-speed rail tender
此次高铁招标
It's about to start
马上就要开始了
you
你
Errors are not allowed
错误是不允许的
How to suppress red language
如何抑制红色语言
The secret method to capture her
夺取她的秘密手段
being confirmed
正在确认中
Based on the security of national assets
以国家资产安全为前提
We must do something.
我们必须做点什么。
The person behind Shoichi
翔一背后的那个人
I'll dig it out
我会把它挖出来
OK
好的
make out
认出
Qin sent me back to the army.
秦地把我送回了军中。
well done
做得好
Thank you, Director Gao.
谢谢你，高局长。
generous compliment
慷慨的赞美
I just haven't said it before
我只是之前没说过
congratulations
恭喜你
you have made progress
你已经进步了
Thanks
谢谢
should be obvious
应该是显而易见的
You said this show sucks
你说这个节目很烂
And this Mr. Zhang
还有这位张先生
I wonder if this has anything to do with it?
我想知道是否与此有关系？
certainly
当然
Xiao Yi and President Zhang
肖毅与张总裁
The relationship between
之间的关系
before us
在我们之前
Everyone investigated
大家都调查了
closer to you
离你更近
reason
原因
intuition
直觉
woman's intuition
女人的直觉
Mr. Zhang
张先生
like a shadow
像影子一样
and school
和学校
He is a true man of action.
他是一个真正的实干家。
Logically speaking
按理说
Madam, we're off work.
女士，我们已经下班了。
Sorry, I have to go now
对不起，我现在得走了
goodbye
再见
Have you done your work?
你的工作完成了吗？
Any time
任何时候
Am I always the last one?
我总是最后一个吗
I suspect you did it on purpose
我怀疑你是故意的
They will come after everyone else has left.
他们会在其他人离开后才来。
I also doubt
我也怀疑
You waited on purpose for me to come.
你是故意等到我来的。
Close again
再次关闭
I agree
我同意
I'm worried that I won't have a delicious late-night snack.
我担心我没有好吃的夜宵。
What do we bring to you today?
今天我们为您带来什么？
expired food
过期的食物
Could you please keep it?
可以请你留下它吗？
I have something good today
我今天有好东西
taste
品尝
Thanks.
谢谢。
Late night snacks were originally something I kept for myself.
夜宵原本是我自己保留的东西。
Now split you in half
现在把你们分成两半
delicious
可口的
Isn’t that what it’s like to be rich?
不就是有钱人的滋味吗？
Should I charge my card?
我应该向我的卡收费吗？
I agree
我同意
Okay, I'll order a cup of ramen.
好吧，我还是点杯拉面。
I invited a friend
我邀请了一位朋友
I am now
我现在是
I'm your friend.
我是你的朋友。
from friends
来自朋友
closer
更近
feel you
感觉你
I feel uncomfortable
我感觉不舒服
You have
你有
drown your sorrow with alcohol
用酒精浇灭你的悲伤
what happened
发生了什么
I can't say what happened
我不能说发生了什么
Recently, it’s closing time
最近，到了打烊的时候
I am very tired
我很累
you?
你？
How are you these days.
这些天你怎么样。
I haven't been here for several days
我已经好几天没来了
Are you busy at work or is your brother busy?
你工作忙还是你弟弟忙？
do you remember?
你是否记得？
He has been looking for a job recently.
他最近一直在找工作。
start working
开始工作
what do you look like?
你长的怎样？
I feel like the world is changing too fast.
我感觉世界变化太快了。
free youth
自由青春
It's 9:05 a.m.
现在是上午 9 点 05 分
He has been dissolute for a long time
他长期放荡
Another job wants him
另一份工作想要他
I want you to cherish it.
我要你好好珍惜。
you?
你？
Have you ever thought about it?
你有没有想过？
Give up your current job
放弃目前的工作
Go find it
去找找吧
Lovely
可爱的
beautiful girlfriend
美丽的女朋友
You are having fun and giving up your life.
你正在享受乐趣并放弃你的生活。
Find a lovely girlfriend
找个可爱的女朋友
You don't have to give up your job
你不必放弃你的工作
Get a feel for your current job
感受一下你现在的工作
It's not fun.
这并不有趣。
I've been working overtime
我一直加班
certainly
当然
but i never thought about it
但我从来没有想过
You must live without worries
你必须无忧无虑地生活
no one is a good girl
没有人是好女孩
You still here
你还在
Turn on the broken switch
打开坏掉的开关
When I was a kid, I was very self-indulgent.
当我还是个孩子的时候，我很自我放纵。
There's still a chance to turn around
还有转身的机会
I have passed
我已经过去了
I've reached the age where I don't care
我已经到了不在乎的年纪
it's never too late
永远不会太迟
let's go
我们走吧
It's too late
为时已晚
work done
工作完成了
Do I want to clean it up?
我要清理它吗？
No
不
They will clean it up tomorrow
明天他们会清理
It's too late now
现在已经太晚了
otherwise
否则
i will send you back
我会把你送回来
Understood
明白了
You get off work so late every day.
你每天下班都这么晚。
Let's go home alone
我们一个人回家吧
that's right
这是正确的
There are many shops on the road
路上有很多商店
very safe
非常安全
but you are a girl
但你是个女孩
I am already a woman
我已经是个女人了
I agree
我同意
How long does it take to get to your home?
到你家需要多长时间？
Can you drive me home?
你能载我回家吗？
Of course go home
当然是回家
we can also
我们也可以
Choose your vehicle
选择您的车辆
Understood
明白了
Take me on your bike
带我骑上你的自行车
able
能
Next time I will prepare a tricycle
下次我准备一辆三轮车
this is a good idea
这是个好主意
Here we are
我们到了
very close
很近
I agree
我同意
Convenient for commuting
方便通勤
sounds good
听起来不错
Why not sit on it?
为什么不坐在上面呢？
Shouldn't a gentleman say no?
绅士不应该拒绝吗？
do not regret
不要后悔
Regret
后悔了
thank you for sending it to me
谢谢你发给我
goodbye.
再见。
Hey
嘿
I haven't been home recently
我最近没回家
what happened
发生了什么
Gao Tianyang suddenly sent me home.
高天阳突然把我送到家里。
I don't feel well
我感觉不太舒服
I didn't go home
我没有回家
Is he starting to doubt you?
他开始怀疑你了吗？
possible
有可能
for safety
为了安全
I went back to my apartment.
我回到我的公寓。
I'll find time to clean it up.
我会找时间清理一下。
take care of yourself
照顾好你自己
Yes
是的
first
第一的
The first philosophy reading template
第一个哲学阅读模板
only one
只有一个
Campus Q&A Community
校园问答社区
many investors
许多投资者
I am very interested
我很感兴趣
But on the other hand
但另一方面
This website is so professional
这个网站太专业了
The audience is not wide
受众并不广泛
So they made me lower
所以他们让我变得更低
User adoption threshold
用户采用门槛
Adopt more users
采用更多用户
I refused
我拒绝了
So this is also my first time reading philosophy.
所以这也是我第一次读哲学。
The capital chain is broken
资金链断裂
Maybe that's why I can't take it anymore
也许这就是我无法再忍受的原因
Yes
是的
You can understand it this way
你可以这样理解
why did you refuse
你为什么拒绝
attractive investment
有吸引力的投资
To be honest, I have never had such a luxury.
说实话，我从来没有享受过这样的奢侈。
Let everyone accept philosophy
让每个人都接受哲学
What do you think of my choice?
我的选择你认为
correct
正确的
I can only say
我只能说
Your choice and the most
你的选择和最
People who work in information technology are different.
从事信息技术工作的人是不同的。
different options
不同的选择
It's a different attitude and understanding.
这是一种不同的态度和理解。
result
结果
I just think
我只是想
Content and practical abilities are the core
内容和实践能力是核心
Keys to creating a website
创建网站的关键
This determines how far you can go
这决定了你能走多远
so
所以
we spent a lot of time
我们花了很多时间
Dynamic passion and way of thinking
充满活力的激情和思维方式
Yes, no matter how many times I say it, I can’t get started.
是的，说多少次都无法开始。
try it yourself
自己尝试一下
you will like it
你们会喜欢的
Yes, I promise
是的，我保证
I think you are a high quality user.
我认为您是一个高质量的用户。
Bring great users
带来优秀的用户
Yes, it's done
是的，已经完成了
congratulations
恭喜你
Thanks
谢谢
From the results
从结果来看
your choice is right
你的选择是正确的
This is hope, this is hope
这是希望，这是希望
even after one year or twenty years
即使经过一年或二十年
I came to a conclusion
我得出一个结论
Thank you for the interview
感谢您接受采访
Thanks
谢谢
pray often
经常礼拜
goodbye
再见
In the live broadcast room just now
刚才的直播间里
Real-time number of viewers
实时观看人数
Break platform records
打破平台记录
Congratulations Mr. Zhou
恭喜周先生
This is real
这是真的
This is everyone's contribution
这是大家的功劳
so
这样
Please go back to your room to rest first.
请大家先回自己的房间休息。
Evening at rooftop restaurant
晚上在天台餐厅
let us celebrate
让我们庆祝一下
Thanks
谢谢
There is an online shopping mall
这里有一个网上购物中心
let's go out and play
我们出去玩吧
I will not go
我不会去
I forgot to invite my friends
我忘了邀请我的朋友
what kind of friends
什么样的朋友
Cool?
酷吗？
take me with you
带我一起走
what's on your mind?
你在想什么？
I have a very urgent matter.
我有一件非常紧急的事情。
You leave, I won’t leave
你走我不走
Don't forget the party tonight
别忘了今晚的聚会
OK
好的
welcome
欢迎
goodbye
再见
Let's eat together
一起去吃
Come on, let's go eat
走吧，我们去吃饭
go
去
walk to eat
步行去吃饭
Xiao Huang Xiao Huang
小黄小黄
I'm going to have dinner.
我要去吃晚饭了。
You go first, I'll be there right away.
你们先走，我马上过去。
OK
好的
Hello, resource room
你好，资源室
Hello
你好
I'm from the technical department
我是技术部的
your computer
你的电脑
Has it been repaired before?
请问之前有修复过吗？
It's convenient to go now
现在去方便
Do you want to check again?
您想重新检查吗？
Now
現在
Tasks assigned by my department
我部门安排的任务
If the computer breaks down again
如果电脑又坏​​了
will be very troublesome
将会很麻烦
Now everyone take a break
现在大家都休息一下
OK, just a second.
好的，请稍等。
OK
行
Hello, technical department
技术部您好
Hello, please come here now.
你好，请现在过来。
OK
好的
It is said that this was the East Factory of the Ming Dynasty.
据说这里是明代的东厂。
invention method
发明方法
Have a nice name
有一个好听的名字
Rain in plum blossom season
梅花季节下雨
I like this name
我喜欢这个名字
Probably not a good experience
可能不是一个好的经历
do you know
你知道吗
Huang Zichen deceived us
黄子晨欺骗了我们
I have no idea
我不知道
if you tell me the truth now
如果你现在告诉我真相
may be next
可能是下一个
not just paper
不只是纸
in a lid
在一个盖子里
maybe you can fight
也许你可以奋斗
Next is the second one
接下来是第二个
able to breathe
能够呼吸
becoming more and more difficult
变得越来越困难
The third
第三个
From the fourth picture to the fifth picture
从第四张图到第五张图
The paper was dry by then.
那时纸已经干了。
Turn each piece of paper over one by one so that the uneven areas are clearly visible.
将每张纸一张一张翻过来，凹凸不平的地方清晰可见。
like a human face
像人脸一样
I'll give you one last chance
我会给你最后一次机会
what on earth did he do
他到底做了什么
There was something wrong with the documents he was holding.
他所持有的文件有问题。
Don't say you don't know
别说你不知道
Dr. Feng’s computer photo
冯博士电脑照片
I stole it.
我偷了它。
The Macau documents were also stolen from me.
澳门文件也被我偷走了。
There is also a report on Mr. Huang's computer.
黄先生的电脑上还有一份报告。
I stole it.
我偷了它。
in the middle
在这中间
what did I do?
我做了什么？
you have no idea
你根本不知道
If a spy asks you, just say so.
如果间谍问你，就这么说。
I really do not know
我真的不知道
I caught Huang Jiaming's attention.
我引起了黄家明的注意。
He went to get the documents
他去拿文件
He did get the papers.
他确实拿到了文件
he showed me
他给我看了
real
真的
You know
你知道的
Is it the result of betraying the organization?
是背叛组织的结果吗？
I know
我知道
if you tell me the truth now
如果你现在告诉我真相
Maybe you don't have to kill me
也许你不必杀我
I really do not know
我真的不知道
What I said is real
我说的都是真的
like
好像
Of course she doesn't know
她当然不知道
I really don't want you to know
我真的不想让你知道
just very stupid
只是非常愚蠢
I believe Huang Zichen
我相信黄子晨
if this is a lie
如果这是谎言
Huang Zicheng is not alone
黄子成并不孤单
behind him
在他后面
There might be an NSA.
可能有一个国家安全局。
National Security Bureau
国安局
work done
工作完成了
I walked through Huangcan
我走过黄灿
goodbye
再见
the person in front of me
我面前的人
I can't see it
我看不了
your expression is
你的表情是
Generally speaking
一般来说
dead for a long time
死了很久了
You were personally chosen by me.
你是我亲自选择的。
I want to give you another chance
我想再给你一次机会
Huang Zicheng
黄子誠
Can be done privately
可以私下进行
Can do small movements
可以做小动作
I didn't realize I was remiss.
我没有意识到我失职了。
but i can't believe it
但我不敢相信
He is a national security agent
他是一名国家安全人员
Huang Zicheng does not necessarily belong to Guoan
黄子成不一定属于国安
But he has an older brother from Guoan.
但他有一个来自国安的哥哥。
high sky sun
高高的天空太阳
You face him every morning and night
你每天早晚都面对他
you should know best
你应该最了解
his situation
他的情况
Huang Zicheng
黄子诚
Is there real fear?
有真正的恐惧吗？
his every move
他的一举一动
Are you a spy player?
你是间谍玩家吗？
You believe Huang Zicheng too much
你太相信黄子成了
us
我们
true partner
真正的伙伴
You are different from him
你和他不一样
Huang Zicheng is an octopus
黄子诚是一只章鱼
You are that thread
你就是那个线程
This is a bridge between us and him.
这是我们和他之间的一座桥梁。
you are always in our hands
你永远在我们手中
Huang Zicheng
黄子诚
What's floating in the air
空中飘着什么
you to him
你对他
Feelings are born
感情是诞生的
But it's dangerous
但这很危险
I dragged him into the water.
我把他拖进水里。
That's stupid
那太愚蠢了
You always thought you were cheating on him
你一直认为你在欺骗他
he has a problem
他有问题
But have you ever thought about it?
但你有没有想过？
from start to finish
从开始到结束
deceived person
被欺骗的人
It's you
是你
Sometimes emotions control people
有时候情绪会控制人
irrational judgment
非理性判断
make stupid moves
做出愚蠢的举动
My wife is here
我老婆来了
Look at the camera
看镜头
jogging
慢跑
take it easy
别紧张
wonderful
精彩的
Be careful
当心
here we go
开始了
received
已收到
look
看
Why did you come to see my sister?
你为什么要来看我姐姐？
You promised.
你保证过。
Don't go to my family
别去找我的家人
And this thing
还有这个东西
Nothing to do with her
与她无关
You promised.
你保证过。
One more one, one more one
再来一张再来一张
I told you
我告诉你了
we don't disturb them
我们不打扰他们
Just give you one
只给你一个
small warning
小警告
your family
你的家人
I got you involved
我让你参与其中
do you understand
你明白吗
I'll give you one last chance
我会给你最后一次机会
Go home and see
回家看看
What is the identity behind Huang Zicheng?
黄子成背后的身份是什么？
behind him
在他后面
Who else is there?
那里还有谁？
Even if Huang Zicheng
即使黄子成
I really rely on national security.
我真的很依赖国家安全。
But he is for us
但他是为了我们
Still very useful
还是很有用的
This will also affect your destiny
这也会影响你的命运
Do you understand it?
你明白了吗？
make out
认出
I lost contact with Yaoyao.
我和瑶瑶失去了联系。
How long
多久了
afternoon
下午
Sent her a few messages
给她发了几条消息
won't come back
不会回来
I called but didn't answer
我打电话但没有接听
The key is the game mission
关键是游戏任务
Not passed yet
还没有通过
I always have a bad feeling.
我总有一种不好的预感。
Task completed
任务已完成
Please call Yaoyao again.
请再给瑶瑶打电话。
Hey Yaoyao
嘿瑶瑶
How are you
你还好吗
It doesn't matter
没关系
what happened
发生了什么
I sent you a message, but you didn't reply.
我给你发了消息，你没有回复。
I can't even answer the phone
我什至无法接听电话
I'm worried something happened to you.
我担心你出了什么事。
when i have lunch
当我吃午饭的时候
I accidentally made soup
不小心熬汤了
Spilled on my phone
洒在我的手机上
my phone is broken
我的手机坏了
It's done now
现在已经完成了
complete
完毕
I replaced it with a new one.
我把它换成了新的。
I just opened
我刚刚打开
I got your call.
我接到你的电话。
you are safe
你很安全
That's it
就是这样
Are you looking?
你在看吗？
Task completed
任务已完成
That's very good
那挺好的
When will you come back.
你什么时候会回来。
2 days left
还剩2天
that person
那个人
when you come back
当你回来时
I will pick you up at the airport.
我会去机场接你。
How did you hear that?
你怎么听到的？
It seems that this feeling is not very strong.
看来这种感觉并不是很强烈。
I am very tired today
我今天很累
That would be good
那样就好了
If you are busy, go to bed early.
如果你很忙，就早点休息。
goodbye
再见
something wrong
有什么不对劲
It seems nothing has changed
似乎一切都没有改变
she knows
她知道
After the task is passed
任务通过后
A little too calm
有点太冷静了
She might be really tired
她可能真的很累
Any time
任何时候
must be cautious
必须保持谨慎
knew
知道了
Please exchange it after returning to your country.
请回国后兑换。
go
去
Yao Yao
姚瑶
Zhouzhuang
周庄
Why don't you go out for a drink?
你为什么不出去喝一杯？
I am a little uncomfortable.
我有点不舒服。
What's wrong?
怎么了？
I feel like I have a cold
我感觉自己好像感冒了
Go home early and rest
早点回家休息
Please ask the front desk later.
请稍后询问前台。
I'll send you some medicine
我给你寄点药
Thanks
谢谢
That's stupid
那太愚蠢了
You always thought you were cheating on him
你一直认为你在欺骗他
People who were deceived from the beginning to the end
从头到尾都被骗的人
It's you
是你
Sometimes emotions control people
有时候情绪会控制人
irrational judgment
非理性判断
your family
你的家人
For you
为你
do you understand
你明白吗
OK
好的
Tianyang Investigation
天洋调查
Rooting electronic equipment
修根电子设备
No abnormality
无异常
two other countries
另外两个国家
Project group user
项目组用户
Arrive at Jinhai
抵达津海
This bid
本次出价
things are important
事情很重要
Keep signage safe
确保标牌安全
core confidential information
核心機密資料
on the last day
在最后一天
Publish to the entire project team
发布给整个项目组
Xu Fei, leader of the translation team
翻译组组长徐飞
and Shu Yan
和舒妍
You must spend your last days well
你一定要好好度过最后的日子
Prepare to work overtime all night
准备通宵加班
receive
收到
thank you for your hard work
感谢你的努力工作
The meeting dispersed
会议散去
On the computer with root repair
在修根的电脑上
various items
各种物品
electronic equipment
電子機器
We investigate one by one.
我们一一调查。
Unable to locate
无法定位
secret leak device
机密泄密装置
Tender coming soon
招标即将到来
People have serious doubts about Shu Yan.
人们对舒妍产生了严重的怀疑。
stay in bidding group
留在投标组
high risk
高风险
But we are now
但我们现在
safe
安全的
Target
目标
Refers to Zhu Yan and Xiao Yi
指的是朱颜和萧毅
evidence of spies
间谍的证据
So you can't catch it
所以你抓不到它
everything now
现在的一切
Everything must go smoothly with the bid.
一切都必须与投标顺利进行。
If we say
假如说
It's really not good
实在是不好
First, suppress speech
首先，抑制言语
What do you think about Tianyou?
对于天佑，你有什么看法呢？
Qin area
秦地区
can you do it
你可以做到吗
give me one more day
再给我一天时间
if i don't make progress
如果我没有进步
we control her
我们控制她
Tomorrow evening
明天晚上
able
能